<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AppointCut</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hair_trend">HairTrend</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">HomePage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="title_activity_augmented_reality">AugmentedRealityActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_augment">AugmentActivity</string>

    <string name="game_view_content_description">Game View</string>


    <string name="high_and_tight">
        The high and tight is a fantastic short haircut for men. Inspired by the military, it is a simple cut that has a masculine and rugged feel.
        Defined by faded or short sides and a slightly longer back and top, the overall look is very neat, helping to achieve a professional appearance.
        You can play around with the length, deciding on very short sides and even a skin fade, or opting for a more traditional and classic approach.
        The high and tight is excellent for a variety of occasions, including more formal ones.
        It is a fuss-free cut that requires almost no style time and can be adapted to suit all hair textures and types.
    </string>

    <string name="spiky_hair">
        Spiky hair is a style that has been popular since the 90s and has a decidedly grunge feel. The appeal of this look today is that it creates a textured appearance and can be adapted to suit hair of various lengths and types.
        The traditional approach would be to opt for defined medium-length spikes. You could also keep them short or choose a messy approach that is much more subtle and natural-looking.
        Spikes will not work with long hair unless you intend to use a strong-hold product, which will make you look more punk.
    </string>

    <string name="taper_fade">
        Few combinations go together as well as the taper fade and slick back hairstyle. The slick back is a timeless cut that can create a polished appearance and is perfect for a gentleman concerned with style.
        It can suit most hair textures and lengths and helps achieve a smart and stylish appearance by brushing back the hair and using products for hold and to create a glossy effect.
        Pairing it with a taper fade can add a modern edge to a classic cut; the hair is gradually cut down the sides and back. This also helps play up proportions.
    </string>

    <string name="undercut">
        In recent years, the undercut has been one of the most popular short hairstyles for men.
        This cut is set to continue its reign while being paired with a variety of looks on top, including pompadours, quiffs, and styles with fringe.
    </string>

    <string name="low_fade">
        One of the best things about fade haircuts is that they can easily be tailored to suit your tastes. For example, if you want a look that’s understated yet still utterly stylish, the low fade haircut makes an excellent choice.
    </string>

    <string name="buzz_cut">
        The buzz cut is a very short hairstyle that is simple and masculine. It is clipped close to the head with a razor and is low maintenance and fuss-free.
        It can highlight your facial features and give off a rugged yet polished appearance. Despite being a basic cut, it is versatile and can be adapted to different hair textures and styles.
        For example, a fresh and modern approach would be to include a lineup or a skin fade, which will give your look more personality and edge.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_part_hair">
        Hair can be parted at the natural part or where you decide. Here’s how to do both.
        The natural part is how hair grows. It’s good to know where this is, even if you don’t use it.
        To find the natural part, comb wet or dry hair straight back. Hold it tight in your hand like a slick style and then gently push hair forward.
        Hair will bubble up a bit. Do this a few times until hair splits into the natural part.

        To create a new part, use a comb for a straight and defined part. Some combs have a pointed tip or tail designed for this. Comb hair back, define a comb line, and separate hair with fingers.
        Line a side part up with the peak of a brow, edge or a brow, or edge of the forehead. For a middle part, use the center of the nose as a guide to approximate the center of the head.
        Some haircuts are too short and/or textured for hair to fall into a part, like crops or buzz cuts.
        Medium and longer styles can create a part with the help of a comb, some blow drying, and hair product.
        If you’re looking to add more volume to a side part hairstyle, try parting hair opposite the natural part.
        Because hair is used to lying in the opposite direction, this adds some volume. Over time, hair can be trained to have a new part.
        Brush it where you want it to go, use heat and product to reinforce the new direction.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_style_short_hair">
        There are more short hairstyles for men to choose from than you would think. Beyond the buzz cut, there is the textured crop, spikes, quiff, slick back, pompadour, and side part.
        Some haircuts can be styled in any one of these looks and others lend themselves to one or two different styles. The great thing about short hair is it grows fast and can easily be changed to try out lots of looks until you’ve found your signature style.
        Short haircuts for men often look like they don’t need to be styled but that is rarely the case. Unless you have a buzz cut or hair that lies just right, skip this. For everyone else, here’s how to style short hair.
        The good news is that short hair does not need much else other than styling. Do say yes to conditioner. Blow dry hair if you want to. But for most guys, a little bit of hair product is all you need.
        The shorter the hair, the less product you need. Start with a small pea-sized amount and work up from there. With almost or totally dry hair, rub the product between the palms to warm up and work into hair thoroughly.
        Finish with a comb for a more polished style like an Ivy League. Or add some trendy texture by pushing hair in different directions, finger combing, and pinching small sections of hair.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_style_short_curly_hair">
        These tips are for short curly hair that is long enough to have some texture. Here’s how to care for hair to hold curls while maintaining their shape. You are probably already conditioning hair but if not, start immediately.
        Curly hair tends to be dry and requires added oils to look its best. Out of the shower, gently squeeze hair dry with a microfiber towel. Cotton may feel soft to the skin has a coarse texture can cause breakage and frizz.
        Special towels for curly hair have a tighter weave that won’t disrupt natural texture. An old t-shirt will also do the trick.
        With damp hair, scrunch a cream product into hair. This helps work product throughout hair without disrupting the curl pattern. Try one of our top recommendations for curly hair products.
        With product thoroughly distributed, let hair air dry to keep that curl shape. Of course, that means you need a great cut that gives curls a flattering shape.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_braid_hair">
        Braids for men can be a number of different things. For long hair, a braid can be another style that keeps hair out of the face. That can be a classic 3-strand braid or more elaborate modern braid.
        For black hair, there are even more cool braided hairstyles that last for weeks or even months. For the longest-lasting and most creative looks, visit a professional.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_perm_hair">
        Perm, short for permanent, provides long-lasting curls. Permed curls don’t fade over time and have to grow out. The trend for permed hair comes and goes and seems to back again. Here’s what you need to know about at-home perms.
        There are two types of perms, alkaline and acid. Alkaline formulas have a pH of 9-9.6 and are best suited for healthy, coarse, and hair that resists curls. Acid formulas have a lower pH between 4.5 and 7 and should be used on dry, color-treated, or damaged hair types.
        In addition to the perm lotion, most kits also contain end papers that protect the tips of hair, a drip guard to protect the face, and neutralizer to stop the perm solution processing. If it doesn’t come with gloves, do find some to protect your hands.
        In addition, you will need perm rods. The lotion prepares hair to take on curl but does not create the shape. That’s where perm rods come in. Hair is wrapped around to define a new shape. Wider rods create waves while thinner rods create tight curls.
        Like all things hair, you can do it at home but for best results, invest in a trip to the salon if you can.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_straighten_hair">
        Transforming curly or wavy hair into straight involves some products, a blow dryer, and brush.
        Start with a heat protectant spray to prevent damage from the blow dryer. The type of brush for straightening hair is a small round brush with bristles.
        This allows you to pull hair taut while blowdrying it, resulting in straight hair. Work from one side to the other until all hair is straightened.
        If it’s not straight enough for your liking, go over hair again with a flat iron. Last, lock it all in with a blast of cold air from the blow dryer and a once over with product for the final style.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">TestActivity</string>

</resources>